<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Money Motivation EXTREME</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="how_to_fiverr1">
        \n\n<b>Offer social media services</b>\n\n People are desperate to get traffic to their websites and they don’t mind paying $5 to drive traffic to their web pages.
        \n\n<b>Write and get paid</b> \n\n If you are able to knock out 400 words in 12 minutes or less, you can rack up a base rate of $25 per hour.
        \n\n<b>Use marketing software to get paid</b>\n\n There are all sorts of traffic generation software that you can use for a few minutes to promote clients’ sites.
        \n\n<b>Researching Work</b>\n\n Get paid to use Google for a research project. As long as you make sure that your research is tightly focused, you should be able to do research in a very short period of time.
        \n\n<b>Making Jewelry</b>\n\n If you have the passion for making handmade gemstone necklaces or personalized bracelets, you can use it to make money on Fiverr.
        \n\n<b>Making Attractive Book Cover</b>\n\n With the right tools and skills, you can earn bucks by designing book covers. Now that eBooks are very popular, you don’t have to print book covers anymore.
        \n\n<b>WordPress Troubleshooter</b>\n\n WordPress can be complicated for many, although it can come naturally and very easily to others.
        \n\n<b>Virtual Assistant</b>\n\n If you choose to do this gig it could include things such as data entry, creating emails, and research, or any other related task.
        \n\n<b>Article Writing</b>\n\n If writing comes naturally to you, this could be a good one for you. Get your hands dirty, make a good portfolio and get into it!
        \n\n<b>Background Removal</b>\n\n Remove background of images of the client. It can easy be done with Photoshop or online sites.
        \n\n<b>Write a review</b>\n\n If you are a fast writer and can knock out a 400 word review in less than 12 or 10 minutes, this can be a great gig to offer.
        \n\n<b>software to produce SEO</b>\n\n There are tons of software that diagnose how healthy a site is in terms of SEO.
        \n\n<b>Use software to find SEO keywords</b>\n\n There are hundred of tools that can help you in SEO Keyword findings… Do it!
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_fiverr">
        \n\n<b>Fiverr is a marketplace where anyone can sign up and sell services from $5</b>
        \n\n<b>That can be anything from…</b>
        \n\n<b>Logo design</b>\n\n There are all sorts of traffic generation software that you can use for a few minutes to promote clients’ sites.
        \n\n<b>Video creation</b>
        \n\n<b>Backlinks</b>
        \n\n<b>Social signals</b>
        \n\n<b>There really is a gig for everyone!</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 1 – Practice Your Skill!</b>\n\n Please do not make a gig unless you are confident being creative and hardworking about!
        \n\n<b>Step 2 – Create Fiverr Gig</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 3 – Creating Your Gig Image</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 4 – Writing Your Gigs Description</b> Follow the steps of those who are working on the same niche as you are on Fiverr.
        \n\n<b>Step 5 – Tags/Keywords</b>\n\n One of the most important parts of your gig is setting up the tags and keywords. \n A lot of people don’t realise this but having your gig tagged correctly is very important to the ranking of your gig in Fiverrs search results.
        \n\n<b>Step 6 – Video-fying Your Gig</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 7 – Promote it over all over the social media</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 8 – BE PATIENT!</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 9 - Bid on Buyers Requests</b>
        \n\n<b>Step 10 - Make more Gigs!</b>
        \n\n<b>DOWNLOAD OUR PDF OF PREMIUM CONTENT ON FIVERR !!!</b>

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_freelancing">
        \n\n<b>Let us Talk About One of the Biggest Website on Freelancing in the Wrold!</b>
        \n\n<b>Freelancer.com</b>
        \n\n<b>Determine what you are good at</b>\n\n Signing up and working at Freelancer.com is absolutely free, but we also have membership upgrades that will greatly help you to earn more, such as getting more bids per month, and a list of skills.
        \n\n<b>Set up your profile</b> \n\n  We can not stress the need for a complete and presentable profile enough. It showcases your personality, resume, portfolio, and skills all rolled into one.
        \n\n<b>Find projects and start bidding</b>\n\n Hundreds of projects and contests in different categories are posted each day. Find the ones you want to work on by regularly checking the Jobs or Contests page. In the jobs page, you will see suitable projects open for bidding. For contests, you simply submit an entry.
        \n\n<b>Work</b>\n\n This might be the hardest but most rewarding step. Before starting work, make sure that both you and the employer are aligned in terms of project scope, deadlines, and milestone payments so there will be no issues along the way.
        \n\n<b>Get paid and earn five-star feedback</b>\n\n Once you get paid, you can withdraw your money via PayPal Wire Transfer, Moneybookers, or your nominated local bank account (works through our Express Withdrawal System). Also, always aim for five-star feedback – the accumulation of great, quality feedback is a great addition to your portfolio.
        \n\n<b>Making Attractive Book Cover</b>\n\n With the right tools and skills, you can earn bucks by designing book covers. Now that eBooks are very popular, you don’t have to print book covers anymore.
        \n\n<b>How To Keep Moving</b>\n\n Once you complete 5-10 projects, it will become very easy for you to get new orders!
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_freelancing1">
        \n\n<b>Upwork.com</b>
        \n\n<b>Define your title</b>\n\n  Ideally, your title should be a two- to three-word summary of your core strengths, with maybe a few enhancing words on either side.
        \n\n<b>Define your tags</b> \n\n  Choosing skills tags is very important because it affects how you are found by potential clients as well as how you are perceived.
        \n\n<b>A clear and good description</b>\n\n  Writing a description can be easily done after you have made a headline and associated tags. When you write your description, try to present arguments for why someone should hire you by focusing on the best pitches first.
        \n\n<b>Take tests</b>\n\n Taking a few tests that are relevant to the work you do is the best way to validate what you claim in your profile description.
        \n\n<b>Do 5-10 small assignments</b>\n\n Be honest, over-deliver, and grow your reputation. Start small by applying for assignments less than $50. Make sure they are given by clients with good feedback and who have spent a good deal of money on freelancers.
        \n\n<b>A Great portfolio</b>\n\n With the work you have done so far, see if you can add a few samples into the portfolio!
        \n\n<b>Larger jobs</b>\n\n Now, it is time to dive doop into the ocean of Larger Jobs, Good Luck!
        \n\n<b>TRY OTHER SITES TOO LIKE, GURU, WORKPERHOUR AND MANY MANY OTHERS OUT THERE!</b>
        \n\n<b>Ask Experienced people regarding your work and which platform will be best for you.</b>
        \n\n<b>Good Luck!</b>
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_youtube">
        \n\n<b>YouTube </b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Why YouTube: </b>\n\n Every day, five billion YouTube videos are watched around the world. And they are not just being watched, they are being devoured. The average YouTube session by any one viewer is roughly 40 minutes, up 50 percent from the previous year, according to Omnicore.
        \n\n<b>Who can add content</b> \n\n Well, YouTube is not just for amateur filmmakers and people videotaping their zainy housepets anymore. Musicians, TV networks, small businesses, and the self-employed all find monetary value in posting their own amazing content on a YouTube channel.
        \n\n<b>How To Earn:</b>\n\n There are two ways to earn money on YouTube: as an advertiser and as an ad platform. As an advertiser, you pay YouTube for Preroll, Bumpers, or TrueView ads that get your videos in front of potential buyers. As an ad platform, you publish videos that are watched enough to host others content as a paid affiliate or YouTube Partner.
        \n\n<b>Work Constantly</b>\n\n DO not STOP, YOUTUBE WANTS YOU TO WORK WITH CONSISTENCY!!!
        \n\n<b>Work Smartly</b>\n\n Learn how build an audience, learn how big YouTubers work, learn how do they promote and last but not least learn SEO!
        \n\n<b>Monetize your videos</b>\n\n Earn 4000 watch hours and 1000 subs, lets complete this milestone.
        \n\n<b>Set up Google AdSense</b>\n\n You can set up Google AdSense for free at the AdSense website. Click the Sign Up Now button to begin creating your account.
        \n\n<b>Market your videos elsewhere</b>\n\n Do not put your videos just on YouTube! Start a blog, make a website or post them on other video or social media sites. The more views it gets, the better.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_youtube1">
        \n\n<b>Set up and build your YouTube channel</b>\n\n Each YouTube account has one channel attached to it. A YouTube account is the same as a Google account, and creating a YouTube account will grant you access to other Google products, such as Gmail and Drive.
        \n\n<b>Add content</b> \n\n Try to upload content that is high quality, and is not super long. (This option can vary depending on what type of content you decide to upload) Also try to upload regularly and stay consistent with your uploads.
        \n\n<b>Gain an Audience</b>\n\n Building an audience is key to increasing your monetization. You need people to watch your ads in order to make any money off of them. There is no one secret to getting more subscribers, just make the best content that you can and they will come to you.
        \n\n<b>Work Constantly</b>\n\n DO not STOP, YOUTUBE WANTS YOU TO WORK WITH CONSISTENCY!!!
        \n\n<b>Work Smartly</b>\n\n Learn how build an audience, learn how big YouTubers work, learn how do they promote and last but not least learn SEO!
        \n\n<b>Monetize your videos</b>\n\n Earn 4000 watch hours and 1000 subs, lets complete this milestone.
        \n\n<b>Set up Google AdSense</b>\n\n You can set up Google AdSense for free at the AdSense website. Click the Sign Up Now button to begin creating your account.
        \n\n<b>Market your videos elsewhere</b>\n\n Do not put your videos just on YouTube! Start a blog, make a website or post them on other video or social media sites. The more views it gets, the better.
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_howto">
        \n\n<b>Let me tell you one thing, if you have done something good in life, teach people how to do that. Inspire
        people why and how to do that! Make Blogger, Wordpress site, YouTube Channel or Twich etc over your work and share with the world!</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Earn?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Work?</b> \n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To do Something?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Learn?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Cook?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Make Breakfast?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Pass some Exam?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To make Something?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To handle stress?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To treat something?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To talk?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To sit in interview?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To prepare for something?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Earn?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Smart Work?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Fight?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Do Public Speaking?</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tell People How To Rest?</b>\n\n

        \n\n<b>AND SO ON AND SO FORTH...</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>GO TO NEXT PAGE TO GET SOME MORE IDEAS: </b>\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_howto1">
        \n\n<b>Other Than That, Make Videos On:</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Ideas...</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Cars - Elaborate according to expense etc...</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Birds - Kinds etc </b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Mobiles - Tech and Price</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Careers</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Jobs</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 People</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Events</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Top 10 Cars</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>     OR      </b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tech Comparison</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Mobile Prices</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Tech Comparison of Mobiles etc and so on..</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Now you have idea on what kind of work you can do.. </b>\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_blogging">
        \n\n<b>Many people are confused over what constitutes a blog over a website. There are certain things to be kept in mind before starting blogging!</b>
        \n\n<b>Blogs are updated frequently.</b>
        \n\n<b>Blogs allow for reader engagement.</b>
        \n\n<b>There are several reasons why entrepreneurs have turned to blogging:</b>
        \n\n<b>Search engines love new content.</b>
        \n\n<b>Blogging provides an easy way to keep your customers and clients up-to-date.</b>
        \n\n<b>A blog allows you to build trust and rapport with your prospects.</b>
        \n\n<b>Blogs can make money.</b>
        \n\n<b>Blogging is flexible and portable.</b>
        \n\n<b>You can spread your ideas.</b>
        \n\n<b>You can inspire people.</b>
        \n\n<b>It is Slow in the beginning</b>
        \n\n<b>It is difficult to remain consistent if you are not motivated.</b>
        \n\n<b>It takes time to rank it.</b>
        \n\n<b>It takes time to learn it.</b>

        \n\n<b>GO TO NEXT PAGE TO LEARN MORE...</b>
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_blogging1">
        \n\n<b>Choose your blogging platform</b>\n\n There are many blogging platforms available but in my mind the choice is clear and simple. I would set up straight away on a WordPress.org site, and I highly recommend it. \nWordPress com – where they host your blog, look after the back end, and give you access to have it on their own domain, it is Free.\n WordPress org – where you have complete control and host the blog on your own server.
        \n\n<b>Secure a domain name</b> \n\n For the next step of starting your blog you’ll need a domain name (your blog’s address) so that you have a home for your blog online. GoDaddy is an example! Here on ProBlogger my domain name is www problogger com – every blog needs its own domain, so it can be easier said than done to find one that isn’t taken!
        \n\n<b>Configure your blog</b>\n\n If you’ve gone with Bluehost as your domain and hosting provider, installing WordPress is super simple, other hosts including inmotion have similar simple install systems for WordPress. \n Once you’ve completed this process, you now have a WordPress blog installed! You started a blog! Congratulations – you’re almost there!
        \n\n<b>Design your blog</b>\n\n Take some free Templete. Learn the basics, give it time and later you can grow into a big blogger!
        \n\n<b>Start creating useful content that serves readers</b>\n\n Help the world, it is just amazing and inspiring! Enjoy your journey!
        \n\n<b>1- What to do Next</b>\n\n Learn how build an audience, learn how big YouTubers work, learn how do they promote and last but not least learn SEO!
        \n\n<b>2- What to do Next</b>\n\n This can help you later in Freelancing like on Fiverr, Freelancer etc.
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_wordpress">

        <b>PRO TIP*: Wordpress is one of the most easy things to learn on internet as well as interesting! So keep it in your list: </b>


        \n\n<b>Hey, Learn the basics by reading the Blogging portion first, then come here...</b>

        \n\n<b>Monetize Your Blog Content</b>\n\n Make Money With WordPress Affiliate Marketing
\n\n            Display Google AdSense on WordPress
\n\n            Use a WordPress Advertising Plugin to Sell Ads Directly
\n\n            Sell Sponsored Blog Posts
\n\n            Get Paid to Write Reviews
\n\n            Earn Money by Flipping Websites
\n\n            Get Public Speaking Gigs as an Influencer
        \n\n<b>Create a Paid Membership Website</b> \n\n Create Restricted Members Only Content
\n\n            Create a Private Forum
\n\n            Make a Questions and Answers Website
        \n\n<b>Sell Physical Products Online Using WordPress</b>\n\n Start an ECommerce Business With WooCommerce
\n\n            Create an Online T-shirt Store With WordPress
\n\n            Create a WooCommerce Dropshipping Store
\n\n            Create an Amazon Affiliate WordPress Shop
        \n\n<b>Become a WordPress Designer or Developer</b>\n\n Develop WordPress Plugins
\n\n            Sell WordPress Themes
\n\n            Sell Graphics on Your WordPress Site
        \n\n<b> Display Google AdSense on WordPress</b>\n\n Google Adsense is an easy way to make money from your blog. All you need to do is add a script from Google to your website and start displaying ads. \nYou will get paid for every time a user clicks on the ad. These are called CPC ads.
        \n\n<b>Start an Ecommerce Business With WooCommerce</b>\n\n Have an idea for your own product? Why not start your own online store? WordPress makes it easy to create a shop or even add a shop to your existing blog using the free WooCommerce plugin. \nI have worked on it and it is very easy and great to use… MUST TRY!

    \n\n<b>GOTO NEXT PAGE TO GET SOME EXCELLENT IDEAS ON HOW TO EARN MONEY FROM WORDPRESS</b>

    </string>


    <string name="how_to_wordpress1">

        \n\n<b>IDEAS - HOW TO MAKE MONEY FROM WORDPRESS</b>
        \n\n<b>Creating and Selling Plugins</b>
        \n\n<b>Develop WordPress Themes</b>
        \n\n<b>Offer WordPress Consulting Service</b>
        \n\n<b>Blog Setup Service</b>
        \n\n<b>Theme Customizations</b>
        \n\n<b>Content Writing</b>
        \n\n<b>Start Your Own Website</b>
        \n\n<b>Monetize Your Blog</b>
        \n\n<b>E-Commerce for your own business</b>
        \n\n<b>E-Commerce for your secondary business</b>
        \n\n<b>Managing others E-Commerce sites</b>
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_aff_mark">
    \n\n<b>What is Affiliate Marketing:</b> \n\n Affiliate marketing is one of the most popular ways
    people make money online and for some it can be a passive income once established. It is a
    strategy where an individual partners with a business in order to make a commission by referring
    readers or visitors to a business’s particular product or service. But that really is quite a
    simple explanation. To be really successful at making money with affiliate marketing there is a
    little more to it.
    \n\n<b>Blogger:</b> In the case of blogging, a blogger will become an affiliate of a selected
    company and make money from being an affiliate by placing a link, button or banner within a blog
    post that will lead the readers to that affiliate products or services.
    \n\n<b>How to Work</b> An example of going the blatant root? Let’s say you are a food blogger
    and one of the companies you are an affiliate of sells food processors. You can write an entire
    post about that food processor including:
    \nBenefits
    \nCapabilities
    \nRecipes where the food processor could be utilized
    \nCost
    \nCare instructions and more
    \nThen you could include a button, link or banner ad that would take the reader directly to that
    product and they could order it based on your recommendations.
    \n\n<b>Examples of Sites:</b> HuffingtonPost.com \n TopTenSelect.com etc

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_aff_mark1">
        \n\n<b>Decide on a business model</b>
        \n\n<b>Create a website</b>
        \n\n<b>Select a niche</b>
        \n\n<b>Find and work with affiliates</b>
        \n\n<b>Drive traffic to your affiliate program</b>
        \n\n<b>It is a huge topic, so I would recommend you a source here</b> \n Learn it on WikiHow!
        \n\n<b>Top Affiliate Marketing Websites</b>\nAmazon Associates\neBay Partners\nShopify Affiliate Program\nClick Bank\nStudioPress Affiliate Website and so on and so forth!
        \n\n<b>If you are going after it, understand it requires a lot of dedication and work! Good Luck</b>
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_gr_design">
        <b>There are certain reasons you should go for it but remember, it has a lot of competition: </b>
        \n\n<b>Design will always be in demand</b>
        \n\n<b>There is no need for a suit and tie</b>
        \n\n<b>You will never stop being inspired</b>
        \n\n<b>Every day is different</b>
        \n\n<b>It can take you in lots of directions</b>
        \n\n<b>You will never stop learning</b>
        \n\n<b>Creativity is fulfilling</b>
        \n\n<b>Life is too short to stay stuck in a job you hate</b>
        \n\n<b>Job security (pretty much every business needs graphic design)</b>
        \n\n<b>It can pay well (if you feel underpaid ask for more, if it is too little, leave or get better and provide more value)</b>
        \n\n<b>Flexibility </b>
        \n\n<b><i>The desire to convey expression, in the visual sense, with the inner satisfaction of having control over the logistics of concept and style, converts people into graphic designers.</i></b>

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_gr_design1">
        \n\n<b>Host a Skillshare class</b>\n\n Skillshare is an online community marketplace for classes. Anyone can apply to teach - and get paid to host - a class. Some classes designers have created are Basics of Photoshop: Fundamentals for Beginners and From Zero to Hero: Learn Graphic Design.\n You get paid based on the number of online students who sign up for your class. Keep in mind, though, you are not allowed to sell your services or other products to your students.
        \n\n<b>Try your hand at consulting</b> \n\n Consultants are often what I like to call experienced doers, aka highly valuable people. If you have a skill you know other people in your field want, sell consulting services that teach other freelance designers how to duplicate your successes.
        \n\n<b>Blog to position yourself as a pro</b>\n\n If you have not started blogging, start now! Blogging costs you time, but it can pay off big. Use your blog to share design advice for businesses or publish helpful design tutorials.
        \n\n<b>Work Constantly</b>\n\n DO NOT STOP, YOUTUBE WANTS YOU TO WORK WITH CONSISTENCY!!!
        \n\n<b>Give away free stuff</b>\n\n Now that you have started blogging, here is one really effective way to drive traffic back to your site: Give away free and, of course, beautifully branded downloadable resources like templates, themes and graphics!
        \n\n<b>Make smart use of LinkedIn</b>\n\n Make smart use of LinkedInLinkedIn may be a lacklustre online destination for creatives, but it is the online network where professionals seek out other professionals most. To land more gigs using LinkedIn, start by sprucing up your profile. Next, start contributing to a few designer-focused groups. Do it and Hope for the best!
        \n\n<b>Freelancing</b>\n\n Get to the First and Second in the list at previous page!
        \n\n<b>Going further</b>\n\n You already have the skills you need to take your freelance design business to the next level. Now its the time to do what designers do best - get creative!
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_online_tutor">
        \n\n<b>I am Sharing a True Story! From, Richard</b>\n\n
        \n\nI’ll admit it, somewhat embarrassingly given my position now; when my brother first said he wanted to tutor students in London from Brazil I was very skeptical - “Well how will that be any use?” I jested.
        \n\nYet, three years later, I am a complete convert! So much so that I spend most of my time now either training online tutors or else blogging about new methods of teaching online!
        \n\nI tutor almost exclusively online - as many as 8 hours a day (I’ve done 12.5 in the busiest months!) and I’ve trained others to earn over £10,000 in a single month using my recommendations below.
        \n\n <b>Software</b>
\n
BitPaper - the online whiteboard created by tutors, for tutors.
\n
Zoom - for free one-to-one, high quality calls, screen sharing, recording and remote control of each others screen!
        \n\n<b>Hardware</b>\n\n I strongly recommend that the tutor has a powerful computer/laptop. Personally, I do not recommend a tablet over a computer. They are fine, but why limit your explanatory power when a computer can do so much more!
        \n\n<b>Students</b>\n\n Once you are ready (and only once you are ready - it shouldn’t take more than a weekend to get set up!) you will need to either convert your students or else find new students to tutor. There are many websites that are exclusively for tutoring online. These are OK to get started, but tend to charge very low hourly rates.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_online_tutor1">
         \n\n<b>Some Best Online Tutoring Platforms</b>\n\n

        \n\n<b>Udemy</b>
        \n\n<b>Tutorroom.net</b>
        \n\n<b>Skooli</b>
        \n\n<b>Wyzant</b>
        \n\n<b>TutorMe</b>
        \n\n<b>Chegg Tutors</b>
        \n\n<b>WizIQ</b>
        \n\n<b>Whatever platform you choose, make sure you consider all the pros and cons.</b>
        \n\n<b>Once Established, tell people about it, use YouTube, Google Ads etc to bring more students!!!</b>

    </string>

    <string name="how_to_e_com">
        \n\n<b>Go To Previous Page and learn about Blogging, Wordpress First then come here back!</b>
        \n\n<b>Coming from Wordpress page of our app, you are already in half-way!</b>
        \n\n<b>One of the hardest parts of growing an ecommerce business is getting enough traffic to your website. Most ecommerce businesses rely on paid ads to generate sales, but this is expensive and cuts into your profit margins.\n\n I recommend focusing on an inbound marketing strategy so you can improve your store’s rankings in organic search results. It takes more time than buying ads but the payoff is greater.</b>
        \n\n<b>Get your products on as many channels as possible</b>\n\n Being in more than one location online is a must if you want to propel your growth.\n“Growing an eCommerce company starts with a diversification strategy, backed with clear channels of distribution and legal enforcement.
        \n\n<b>Invest in the right software from the start.</b>\n\n Choosing the right platform for your ecommerce business is a serious decision. Take the time to do your homework first before you commit.
        \n\n<b>Invest in search marketing</b>\n\n Learn all you can about SEO and keyword-specific industry topics that you are in before you launch your shop.
        \n\n<b>Some Final Thoughts on Ecommerce</b>\n\n There are many ways you can grow your online store, it just takes time, energy and money. There are no shortcuts, but the payouts can be worth it. The market opportunities are still huge, so don’t despair. If you have a killer product and are willing to put some serious effort into your store, the possibilities are endless.
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_e_com1">
        \n\n<b>How to make E-commerece Successful!!!</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>Don’t rush the launch.</b>
        \n\n<b>Put the focus on the user.</b>
        \n\n<b>Keep it cheap in the start.</b>
        \n\n<b>Test absolutely everything.</b>
        \n\n<b>Update Daily/Frequently</b>
        \n\n<b>Work closely with social media team.</b>
        \n\n<b>Incorporate social elements.</b>
        \n\n<b>Go mobile.</b>
        \n\n<b>Stay on top of SEO.</b>
        \n\n<b>Collect information.</b>
        \n\n<b>Continue evolving.</b>
        \n\n<b>Be Flexible </b>
        \n\n<b>Keep focus on Events!</b>
        \n\n<b>Bring Sales!</b>
        \n\n<b>Be Polite and Himble to Customers.</b>

          </string>


    <string name="how_to_data_entry">
        \n\n<b>Data Entry</b> Online Data Entry Jobs from Home Without Investment.
        There is no doubt that data entry job is one of the most simple opportunity for extra income. People can work on offline and online data entry jobs and earn 200 dollars to 1000 dollars per month.\n
        Your income depends on the type of data entry work, time you spent, your qualification, your typing speed etc.\n
        We will explain you about each data entry jobs you can do from home without any investment so that you can earn maximum earning from this work.\n\n
        <b>Types of Data Entry Jobs</b> \n
        1. Captcha Entry Job\n
        2. Copy and Paste\n
        3. Basic Typing Job\n
        4. Content Writing\n
        5. Proofreading and Copy writing
        \n and many more!
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_data_entry1">
        \n\n<b>Data Entry</b> Top Websites to Earn by Data Entry!
        1. SmartCrowd\n
        2. 2Captcha\n
        3. ClickWorker\n
        4. OneSpace\n
        5. Indeed
        \n\n<b>SmartCrowd:</b> LionBridge SmartCrowd is a part of Business Process Sourcing company that deals with community management. They have over 100,000 cloud workers from all over the world working for them on regular basis.
        \n\n<b>2Captcha:</b> This company might be offering you the easiest way to earn money from Internet. That’s right, you get paid to do CAPTCHA solving.
        \n\n<b>ClickWorker:</b> ClickWorker started as an experimental project launched by NASA that hired workers to participate in scientific data work.
        \n\n<b>OneSpace:</b> OneSpace is basically a Software platform that provides workflow automation solutions to businesses.
        \n\n<b>Indeed:</b>Indeed.com is one of the biggest job search engines on the world wide web. They even have their country based search engines that let you search for local jobs.


        \n and many more!
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_dev_apps">
        \n\n<b>Develop Your Apps</b>\n\n
        \n\n You can develop your own applications but remember that it is not an easy task to create a good android or ios application. \n
        Yet there are certain websites that will make an app for you easily but they take their share. If you seriously want to get into app dev, learn some programming language!\n
        After that install Android Studio and follow some good tutorials! \n
        Over 18% of android app developers earn over $5,000 per month, and the same amount is earned by 25% of iOS app developers. Video game apps are making money in millions.\n
        You can learn android development getting to android development courses on YouTube and also by <b>Udacity</b>.\n\n
        <b>Udacity</b>
        \n\n This course is part of the Android Basics Nanodegree by Google. Learn the basics of Android and Java programming, and take the first step on your journey to becoming an Android developer! This course is designed for students who are new to programming, and want to learn how to build Android apps.
        \n Just search on Google, Udacity Andorid Nanodegree Program!
    </string>


    <string name="how_to_dev_apps1">
        \n\n<b>What is Needed: </b>\n\n “Android is a Linux Kernel-based open source operating system developed by Google. Which is mainly used in Smartphones, Tablets, Smartwatches and Android TV.”
        \n\n<b>Knowledgeable in JAVA: </b>\n\n JAVA is one of the most important designing tools for android app development. Learning design with JAVA can be a most useful and important thing to solve any kind of programming or designing problems.
        \n\n<b>A Good Developer: </b>\n\n To become a successful Android App Developer need persistence, determination, hard work and practice of knowledge and skills in a proper way along with the aim to become an Android App Developer.
        \n\n<b>Use Open-Source: </b>\n\n After learning to develop an android app most of the developers creating small plugins or libraries for their own app.
        \n\n<b>Make a good design: </b>\n\n Great product with a poor design is not going to work properly. In today’s time design matter most. A good and catchy design is able to attract more users.
        \n\n<b>Discuss with other developers: </b>\n\n Try to attend the social meeting of developers or meet other developers personally and spend a little time to discuss with them. Because this is the easiest way to know more. It will help to learn and grow you more.

    </string>


    <string name="how_to_ur_self">
        \n\n<b>1. Watch Less TV, and Choose More Positive Shows</b> \n\nTo make matters worse, these people get hooked and spend a big chunk of their time indulging in it. Most of the stuff on television today teaches us little to nothing about becoming a better person. Fortunately, this is slowly changing and there is an increasing influx of programs that can teach us a lot. Pleasee watch positive things!
        \n\n<b>Read Books or eBooks</b>\n\nReading is a fantastic way to invest in yourself. It also is a relatively cheap activity and can even oftentimes cost nothing. With the advent of the Kindle, iPad and Nook, it is even easier to find great reading material.
        \n\n<b>Get Rid of Toxic Friends</b> \n\nHaving good friends is an important aspect of life. But having friends who are a positive influence is even more important.
        \n\n<b>Find a Mentor</b>\n\n If you are serious about investing in yourself and your future, find someone to mentor you, especially in a field you want to excel in.
        \n\n<b>Learn Something New and Take a Class</b>\n\n You should always be learning a new skill or process. That is what successful people do constantly. They are where they are at because they are always improving themselves. If you do not make it a point to keep learning, you are stagnant and getting left behind in a world that is constantly changing.
        \n\n<b>Plan Your Day and Week</b>\n\n After you set your goals, it is important to plan how you are going to achieve it. Goal-setting is the act of deciding your destination. Planning, on the other hand, is similar to determining how you are going to get there. It is the route you are going to take to your destination.
        \n\n<b>Exercise</b>\n\n This one is a no-brainer! By exercising regularly you will be investing in a habit that creates a healthy mind and a healthy body. The benefits of exercise include disease prevention, better mood, lower body-fat and weight, increased energy, better sleep, and an improved sex life.
        \n\n<b>Do not Drink Alcohol Please</b>\n\nToo much alcohol greatly diminishes your ability to be mindful and productive. It also is expensive. Do no waste your-self please friend!
        \n\n<b>Challenge Yourself and Do Things That Are Difficult</b>\n\nHuman nature is such that people tend to shy away from doing things that they consider to be difficult or challenging, even if they know those activities are good for them. Make an effort to be aware of your way of thinking, and challenge yourself.
        \n\n<b>Forgive</b>\n\nFORGIVE, BUT DON NOT FORGET!!!
        \n\n<b>Love Your-Self</b>\n\nThis is one of the key elements of investing in yourself. Make an effort to love yourself unconditionally by using daily affirmation, self-reflection, and paying close attention to your thoughts and beliefs. A person who loves himself or herself is more likely to invest in themselves and make better decisions.
        </string>


    <string name="how_to_ur_self1">
        \n\n<b>The motto that I’ve built my life around is “One Brick A Day.” </b>
        \n\n<b>1.Invest in more time. </b> \n\n The very first place to start, in my opinion, is to give yourself more time.
        \n\n<b>2.Invest in your health. </b> \n\n Fitness was the very first place I started with self improvement.
        \n\n<b>3.Invest in your interests.  </b> \n\n Everyone talks about “finding your passion” but if you don’t know what it is, what the heck do you do? Simple. Start following your interests. When you find something that peaks your interest, follow that feeling.
        \n\n<b>4.Invest in your long term thinking. </b> \n\n This is a seemingly simple topic but too many people over look it. Ask 100 people what their current goals are or who they want to become and watch their baffled looks. We are so immersed in technology today that not enough people spend time thinking about who they are and who they want to become. If you just put 1 hour to thinking about this per week, you’ll be ahead of MOST people.
        \n\n<b>5.Wealthy people “First Learn, then they remove the L”</b> \n\n They learn what they have to learn, they eat up knowledge they focus on increasing the knowledge they have and increasing it, they are not satisfied with basic answers and strive for excellence in knowledge because the best investment is investment in yourself and they invest in themselves and reap the rewards.


    </string>


    <string name="how_to_uber">
        \n\n<b>Drive for money 9 reasons it is easy to make money with Uber</b>
        \n\n<b>Set your own hours. When you drive with Uber, you are in charge of your schedule</b>
        \n\n<b>Work any time. Uber is available 24/7.</b>
        \n\n<b>Make more money during peak hours.</b>
        \n\n<b>Get paid instantly.</b>
        \n\n<b>Find work around the world.</b>
        \n\n<b>Earn money your way.</b>
        \n\n<b>Get Bonuses.</b>
        \n\n<b>Manage your money.</b>
        \n\n<b>Get in-app directions.</b>
        </string>

    <string name="how_to_uber1">
        \n\n<b>1. As an Uber driver, you can set your own schedule</b>\n\n If you’re looking to maximize your earnings, you’ll need to do your research. You should avoid chasing surge pricing, and instead keep meticulous records of the best times and places to work.
        \n\n<b>2. Uber rating systems have a surprisingly have a big effect on drivers</b>
        \n\n<b>3. You probably won’t make as much money as a driver as Uber says!</b>
        \n\n<b>4. Track your costs</b>
        \n\n<b>5. Uber drivers used to be able to lease a car through Uber.</b>
        \n\n<b>6. Angry passengers are part of your job.</b>
        \n\n<b>6. Rating System: </b> The rating system you have likely noticed as a passenger will become more significant when you become an Uber driver. The system is there to encourage good behavior on the part of passengers and drivers, and both parties can rate one another on a five-star scale at the end of the ride.

        </string>

    <string name="how_to_udemy">
        \n\n<b>UDEMY</b>
        \n\nUdemy is definitely a great place to start. Then if you master the art of course creation and sales, bring it inhouse so you have complete ownership and commission on all sales. The amount of money you can make on Udemy will heavily depend on the type of course you create and how much you actually promote it.
        \n\nIf you really want to make money with Udemy, you will need to spend a lot of time on their site and see what is working best in terms of demand and sales. Their INSIGHTS tool will help with this as well.
        \n\nFree Courses: The reason why many courses are free, is to help bring awareness of the course and to increase enrollment and reviews when the course first goes live. Once there are a decent amount of students and reviews for a course, it can then be switched over to a paid course that will earn money.
        \n\nJust like anything you sell on the internet, you must have buyers. Advertising is the only way to effectively do that.
        \n\nYou must brand yourself as an authority on the topic, and start making yourself known. Social media is a good place to start, and find groups and forums that discuss your topic. These things will take time, but do not lose hope, keep striving.
        </string>


    <string name="how_to_udemy1">
        \n\n<b>PROMOTE UDEMY COURSE: </b>
        \n\n<b>1. Get positive reviews from friends and family</b>\n\n Once your course has launched, the first step to promoting your course is to get at least five positive reviews for your course.
        \n\n<b>2. Send emails to your audience</b> \n\n If you have an email list, this should be one of your top marketing priorities for your Udemy course.
        \n\n<b>3. Promote your course on your blog</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>4. Socialize it</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>5. Add a promotional video on your YouTube channel</b>\n\n
        \n\n<b>6. Optimize your course for search engines</b>\n\n


    </string>

</resources>
